## Marijn van der Zee

Scrum Master (independent contractor, available)

marijn@serraict.com

### Summary

I love to guide software teams on their journey to deliver valuable software and becoming a great team. I enjoy working with the team, but as important is helping the organization to create an environment where teams can shine.

I am a Scrum Master, agile developer, pragmatic student, team player and coach and have been active in the field of software development for well over ten years.

## Experience

#### **Owner at Serra ICT Diensten**

November 2009 - Present

Serra helps organizations to grow great software teams that reliably deliver valuable software.

#### Consultant (independent contractor) at Logiqs Agro

January 2011 - Present

#### Scrum Master (independent contractor) at Raad van State (Dutch Council of State)

May 2016 - June 2017 (1 year 1 month)

Ensuring that Scrum is understood and enacted by the Scrum Team and the Raad van State organisation.

#### Agile Coach (independent contractor) at TransFollow BV

January 2016 - March 2016 (2 months)

Guiding the Scrum Master, Product Owner, two agile teams and the organisation on their journey to deliver the TransFollow platform for exchanging consignment information.

#### Scrum Master TransFollow (independent contractor) at TransFollow

January 2015 - December 2015 (11 months)

Ensuring that Scrum is understood and enacted by the Scrum Team and the TransFollow organisation.

#### Design Team Lead (ad interim) at Beurtvaartadres BV

April 2014 - January 2015 (9 months)

Coordinating activities for the design team working on the TransFollow project. www.transfollow.com/ - the standardised digital consignment note.

#### **Consultant (independent contractor)**

August 2010 - June 2012 (1 year 10 months)

Developing software and coaching the development team.

#### **Software Engineer (independent contractor)**

March 2010 - December 2011 (1 year 9 months)

Developing some small applications, mainly for the web.

#### **Software Architect (independent contractor)**

January 2010 - July 2010 (6 months)

Designing an architecture for a labor registration application to be used in greenhouse horticulture.

Advising the development team during inception, elaboration and construction phases.

#### Systems Analist and Software Architect at Logiqs Agro

September 2005 - September 2009 (4 years)

Technical lead for the application suite Dat-A-Control, a set of applications for controlling various production and logistic processes in automated pot plant nurseries; best compared to MES/WMS systems known from other industries. Project management.

#### Web Developer at Quel Business Information BV

2001 - 2004 (3 years)

Part-time web developer.

#### Education

#### **Delft University of Technology**

MSc, Mechanical Engineering, specialization Transportation Engineering and Logistics, Mechanical

Engineering, specialization Transportation Engineering and Logistics, 1998 - 2005

Activities and Societies: DSBV Punch (Basketball); Dispuut Transportkunde

**Praedinius Gymnasium Groningen** 

VWO, 1992 - 1998

Nederlandse Basketball Bond

Basketball Trainer 4, 2012 - 2013

Scrum.org

PSM III, PSPO I, PSD I, Scrum, 2015 - 2024

# Marijn van der Zee

Scrum Master (independent contractor, available)

marijn@serraict.com



Contact Marijn on LinkedIn